<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hacking in Style</title><link>https://synxb.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Hacking in Style</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://synxb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oxfords or Brogues? An Overview of Shoe Design</title><link>https://synxb.github.io/post/information/shoe_style_overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synxb.github.io/post/information/shoe_style_overview/</guid><description>The Modern Styling of Dress shoes Over the past 100-200 years the styling of dress shoes really has not varied much, if at all. High quality shoe makers will attest to the longevity of the classic styles and designs. As long as you stick within the bounds of the article you will be guaranteed a shoe that will never go out of style.
What are the main shoe styles No matter the maker or designer a dress shoe/boot will fit into one of the categories below.</description></item><item><title>The Different Types of Shoe Construction</title><link>https://synxb.github.io/post/information/different_types_of_shoe_construction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synxb.github.io/post/information/different_types_of_shoe_construction/</guid><description>Introduction There are 3 main techniques when it comes to making shoes:
The cemented/glued Shoe The Blake Stitch Shoe The Goodyear Welted Shoe The latter two being over 150 years old, it really shows that traditional shoe making has withstood the test of time.</description></item><item><title>Herring Charles II Oxfords</title><link>https://synxb.github.io/post/reviews/herring_charles_2_oxford_black/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synxb.github.io/post/reviews/herring_charles_2_oxford_black/</guid><description>Introduction The Black Cap-Toe Oxford is the most elegant and traditional shoe a man can own. This model is styled by English shoe distributor Herring and made by Alfred Sargent. Available in a Black Calf and an Oak Calf, this shoe is incredibly versatile and can be worn in nearly all situations. It is crafted using traditional English shoe-making techniques, if taken care of properly, this shoe will last for years to come.</description></item></channel></rss>